<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kubenertes on Useful PHP Tricks, Laravel Tips, Tricks and Best Practices</title><link>https://blog.phpguru.net/tags/kubenertes/</link><description>Recent content in kubenertes on Useful PHP Tricks, Laravel Tips, Tricks and Best Practices</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 12:08:31 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.phpguru.net/tags/kubenertes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>K8s Labs 001 Building a Kubernetes Cluster With Kubeadm</title><link>https://blog.phpguru.net/post/k8s-labs-001-building-a-kubernetes-cluster-with-kubeadm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 12:08:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.phpguru.net/post/k8s-labs-001-building-a-kubernetes-cluster-with-kubeadm/</guid><description>Forehead
This lab will allow you to practice the process of building a new Kubernetes cluster. You will be given a set of Linux servers, and you will have the opportunity to turn these servers into a functioning Kubernetes cluster. This will help you build the skills necessary to create your own Kubernetes clusters in the real world.
Steps Details Terminologies containerd Reference A CloudGuru Building a Kubernetes 1.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Hands on Labs</title><link>https://blog.phpguru.net/post/kubernetes-hands-on-labs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 11:00:23 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.phpguru.net/post/kubernetes-hands-on-labs/</guid><description>Glossary Lab 001: Building a Kubernetes 1.27 Cluster with kubeadm Lab 002: Deploy a static web application built with ReactJS on your k8s cluster References K8s Cheatsheet</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Complete Course</title><link>https://blog.phpguru.net/post/kubernetes-complete-course/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 09:09:35 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.phpguru.net/post/kubernetes-complete-course/</guid><description>Overview 🔥 What is Kubernetes 🔥 ► What problems does Kubernetes solve? ► What features do container orchestration tools offer?
What Kubenertes is? Open source Container Orchestration Tool Developed by Google Helps you mange containerized applications in different deployment environments: physical, virtual machine, cloud, hybrid What problem does Kubenertes solve? 1st problem: The need for a container orchestration tool
Trend from Monolith to Microservices Increased usage of containers Demand for a proper way of managing those hundreds of containers What features do container orchestration tools offer?</description></item></channel></rss>